All right, everybody in this section we're going to do is focus in on error handling.
So there are multiple different things that can occur within our application that could trigger an error.
Now, we're going to look at a multiple throughout the section.
However, I'm going to go ahead and focus in on one very specific and obvious error in this video.
And that is, well, what if a user decides to go to a page that does not really exist within our pages
directory?
So right now we all really only defined three different routes the home page and the car display page
as well as the car detail page.
But what if the user decides to go and they can very easily do this to, you know, local host, 3000
slash banana and I'm going to go ahead and press enter.
And you can see here this actually triggers an error and specifically it triggers a404 error.
And that's exactly what this is.
So if you know your status code, four or four stands for not found.
And specifically in this case, we have a page not found error and we do not understand this path right
over here.
Now, Knox is actually nice enough to give us this page right off the bat.
So any time we get this particular error, this is what we get.
And we have this nice, neat button that will allow us to go back home.
However, in most applications, we're not going to want to have this kind of default nux page.
We're going to probably want to have our own custom page.
So how can we create our own custom error page?
Well, this is what we're going to do.
So write in the root directory, not in the page's directory.
In the root directory we're going to create a file called error dot to view.
And the name is very important.
It has to be called error dot view.
And then in here we're going to define our template.
So we're going to say div.
And then over here we're going to go ahead and say H one and we're just going to say error for now.
And what ends up happening is any time we have an error, whether it's a404 page error or any other
error that we might potentially have, it's going to go ahead and show this template right over here.
And to prove it to you, if I were to refresh, you can see now we have this blank screen and if I were
to zoom in, you can see this error state right over here.
So now what we can do is we can actually just make this a little bit prettier.
So let's just add a little bit of style.
So I'm going to say flex height screen.
We'll say justify center items, item center, and that should center everything right in the middle,
which is pretty nice for me.
And we're also, say flex calls just so we can change the direction.
And then over here, we can have text Excel, just make it nice and big over here where I'll just change
it to 404.
So we'll have 404 like so.
And we can also small.
We'll can change the color if we want, but I don't really want to do that.
And over here we can also have a message.
So some sort of message so I can say class mt7 so we can have some margin on top and then Excel or text
for Excel.
And we'll just say Page not found something like that.
So Page not found.
And then over here, let's also have a button that will allow us to go back.
So go back.
So I know we pretty much completely replicated what they had here.
So and their styles were definitely a lot better than us.
But what I'm trying to show you is that we can have our own custom page by utilizing this error dot
view.
So let's go ahead and actually finish this off and then we'll talk about another thing a little bit
later.
So I'm going to just go ahead over here in the button.
Let's just make this nice and rounded.
Let's also add a margin top seven E to excel B, g dash blue 400 px7p, y four and then text white.
So we're going to go ahead and add that.
And now we have this cool little button.
And what I want to do is I'm going to click on this button.
I want to go back to the home page and we know how to do this now.
So we're going to say script setup, let's create a function.
I'm going to say const handle.
I'm going to say handle, return, handle, return or what we'll say handle error.
And then over here, we'll just very simply say, I want to go back.
So I'm just gonna say navigate to I'm going to say Slash.
So we're going to go over here.
And we're going to say it's click or we're going to go and we're going to say, handle air.
All right.
So let's go ahead and save this.
And now if I click on it, you can see I go right back.
So again, I have created basically a much uglier version of the original.
However, again, we can customize it to the way that we want.
Maybe for our car website we have like a sad car face or something like that, so we can customize it
the way that we want.