So whether you have built the UI elements with me or you have completely skipped that section and downloaded
the source code, you should have this code right over here, opened up inside of a code editor.
So this right here is a typical Knox application.
It is completely boilerplate and empty.
All that we have here is this HTML directory that contains three different HTML files that is going
to contain all of our HTML as well as our CSS for all of the different pages and components within our
application.
So now let's actually go ahead and start adding it within our Knox application.
So let's go over here and do an NPM install.
If you haven't done that already and you don't have your node modules and then do an MPM run dev inside
of your terminal, So go over here and do an MPM, run dev in order to run your application.
Now, as soon as you run your application, you can see here that it tells you the ports that it is
going to listen on.
Now I already have port 3000 being used so for me it actually allocated 3002.
However, for you it will probably be 3000 if it is indeed not used.
Nonetheless, you can just go over here and figure out exactly what it is.
So now what you can do is you can go to localhost 3002 for me.
And you can see here that there is a completely empty page.
And now what we want to do is we want to add multiple pages within our application.
Because you can see here, if I were to go to the home page, you can see that we have this home page
right over here.
If I go ahead and search, it takes me to this page.
And then if I go over here and let's say I click on this porch, it takes me to another page.
So what we need to do is add routing within our Nook's application, and we're going to begin very,
very simply with routing for the home page.
And this is going to have a very specific route of slash.
So just the home page is as soon as we write the domain and we don't have any other paths, we want
to hit this home page right over here and show the nav bar as well as the car hero.
So that is exactly what we want to do.
So again, once we go to local host 3000 and then there's no other paths, that is what we want to hit.
So let's actually go back to our Nook's application right over here.
And you can see within our Nook's application we only actually have one view file, which is the app
dot view, and I can go right over here and I could just say H one and I can say hello like so.
And if I were to go back to my application and were to zoom in a little bit, you can see that we get
Hello, which is nice.
Okay, so it seems that the home page, we have to add all of our different components within this page
right over here or this file right here.
But that's actually not the case.
So what happens if I go to, let's say, local host, 3002 slash cars, for example, if I were to enter
this, you can see I still get hello.
And if I were to go to another path, slash whatever, I still get this component and this app dot view
file.
So this app dot view file is going to be a very temporary file that we're going to have.
And what it does is it just well, it matches with all different routes.
It treats our application kind of like a single page application and it matches every single particular
route.
And it's like we don't even have routing at all.
If we do want to add routing, what we're going to do is not define any code like we do in view, but
instead what we're going to do is add a folder, a very specific folder in the root directory of our
Linux application.
And this folder is going to be called pages, and it absolutely needs to be called pages because Knox
is going to understand exactly what this folder is doing and it's going to treat all of the different
files within it very specifically so that it can add routing to our app.
So over here we're going to add pages.
And then what I'm going to do is I'm going to create a new file called Index Dot View, and this is
actually going to be the new component that is going to be rendered whenever we go to the home page.
Root So whenever we go to the home page, which is just going to be the slash root, we're going to
render this index dot view.
So let's go over here and I'm going to go ahead and just grab this template.
I'm going to go ahead and paste it in here and we're just going to have our typical hello.
So let's go back over here and let's just see what happens.
So now you can see right away that we're getting some sort of error.
And what I highly suggest you do is whenever we create something like this, let's just close our our
terminal and run back the Linux again.
And so let's refresh this.
So as soon as I refresh, you can see we're getting the loading state, blah, blah, blah.
Come on.
They could forever.
And there we go.
So you can see right away.
Now, when I go to this random route, we're actually getting a 404 page, which is pretty interesting.
So let's actually go over here now to local host 3002.
And now you can see that we have this.
Hello.
Whenever I go to again, another path, we get a404 page.
So it seems as though that this file based routing is indeed working.
Now, one thing that we can actually do here is within the app view, what we can do is we can add a
Knox page component, and this right here is going to be a very specific component that is going to
detect exactly what view file it needs to render.
So this Nook's page is going to figure out what path that we're in.
If we are on the slash path, then it's going to go look at the page's directory.
It's going to look for the indexed view and it's going to go ahead and render this right over here.
So it's going to render this component here.
And why this is nice is that now what we can do is we can add other things on top of it or below it.
So for example, we can add a nav bar, So we're going to say here, nav.
And then over here, we can add a footer.
So footer like so we can say footer like that.
So now we can have nav and then hello and then footer like so, so we can actually kind of customize
exactly what we have.
But for now we'll just leave it like this with the Nux page.
So that's pretty much it.
But of course now we need to go ahead and actually populate our components or our, our page with these
components with this nav bar that's humongous and have to zoom out so you can actually see it well.
So it's nav bar as well as this hero.
So let's do that in the next video.