So we created this file.
However, we have a pretty major problem.
And the last section I told you that this is going to be an error file that all different errors are
eventually going to render.
So it's always going to render this template right over here.
So it's not necessarily always going to be a 404 error.
You could just have a 400 error or a 403 error or some other error that we can potentially have.
And it's also not necessarily always going to be a page not found error.
So right over here, it's not really a good idea to have these values be static.
Instead, they should be dynamic depending on the error.
And how can we accomplish this?
Well, we can accomplish this by utilizing the use error composable.
So this is a built in composable that we can auto import and it's going to give us information about
the error that we currently have.
So I can say here const error is equal to use error and again this is a built in composable and this
right here is going to give us an error object that's going to have a bunch of different different information.
Now, specifically, one piece of information that we really need is the status code.
So I'm going to say error status code.
And then right over here I can also say error dot message.
So I'm going to go ahead and actually save this.
And now let's go to a different URL.
And you can see we pretty much get the exact same thing.
We still get a 404.
We've got actually a nicer message page not found and it tells us exactly what the route is.
But now this is dynamic so we can actually reuse this throughout our app.