In this video.
What I would like to do is populate this page with all of the necessary components, like the nav bar
component as well as the hero.
So let's actually go over here and we're going to have to actually start creating some of these components.
And let's begin with the nav bar, which is going to be by far the simplest thing that we have thus
far.
So I'm going to go ahead and create another directory and I'm going to call this directory components.
Now, the name of this is also extremely important because we're going to place all of our components
in here.
And as soon as we place Vue files in here, Knox is actually going to know that they're components because
they're inside of this directory right over here.
And it's going to do some special magic that we're going to see a little bit later.
So I want to go over here and I'm going to create a nav bar dot view file.
And we actually already well wrote out the nav bar HTML.
So if we go to the home page, we can just go ahead and just grab this right over here.
So where over here, you can see it starts out enough, bar ends and nav bar.
So just grab this HTML as well as CSS, and then we're going to go over to our nav bar.
We're going to create a templates and we're going to go ahead and just paste this in right over here.
So this is our nav bar.
And now what I want to do is I actually want to use it within the index dot view file.
So typically what we would do is we would actually import in that nav bar component.
So we would have some sort of script tag right over here.
We'll say script setup and we would just say very simply, import nav bar, and then we can say from
we'll move back to directory, we'll go components and we'll just say nav bar, and then right over
here we can just go ahead and just render this Navarre component.
So that's typically what we would do.
And you can see that this still works.
The cell is a viable solution.
However, we actually do not need to do all of this inside of a Knox application.
And that's because whenever we place something within the components directory, Knox is going to understand
that it is indeed a component.
And whenever we actually just go ahead and render that component within a page or another component,
it is going to go ahead and auto import for us.
So over here I can actually remove all of this bloat and I can just go ahead and save this.
And it's going to be smart enough to basically will do this under the hood.
So we're going to go ahead and just save that.
And now just to prove to you that we still have our nav bar Tata, we still have our nav bar.
This is pretty incredible and can make our code significantly cleaner.
All right.
So now let's actually go ahead and do the exact same thing, but this time for the car hero.
So I'm going to go ahead and create another another component.
And I'm going to call this car hero.
I'm going to say car hero dot view, and I am going to go over to where are we?
I'm going to go over to the home page and I'm going to grab this car hero.
So you can see here we have this comment here saying car hero.
We also have this end comment that also says car hero.
So we could just grab all of the HTML within that and just copy that and we can go over to Car Hero
and we can go ahead and just create a template and just paste in all of that HTML.
And now very simply, look at this.
I can just go here and just say Car Hero, the exact same name of the file, and then tada, we get
our car hero.
How cool is that?
Now, one thing that I actually also want to do is I want to separate this home search bar.
So if you go to our final or if we go to this version over here, actually, I want to separate this
search bar into its own component, because this search bar has quite a bit of functionality within
itself.
And I would like to kind of isolate it.
So let's go ahead and do that.
That should be pretty easy.
I'm going to call this car search bar.
Or going say doctor view.
And then over here, I'm going to go ahead and just kind of cut everything within this.
So within this comments, let's just go ahead and just cut everything out.
And we can also we'll cut this out a little bit later.
We're going to create a template.
And then over here, we're going to create that car search bar.
And now this time, we're inside of a component, not a page.
We can still treat it.
We can still basically do the exact same thing.
We can just say here now car search bar, and we can go ahead and just save that.
And if I were to go back to my application, it still renders that search bar.
And if I were to, of course, comment it out, just to prove to you, let's go ahead and just comment
this out.
You can see that it is gone.
Tada!
Awesome.
All right.
So now we can just remove this.
We don't need that anymore.
So one thing that I also want to quickly note is that you can see here that within our component directory,
it seems that for at least for these two components here, we have kind of a very similar naming structure.
So we have car and then hero car and then search bar.
And later on we're going to have a lot of other components are going to follow that exact same naming
structure like car card or car sidebar or whatever.
So one thing that's actually nice is that what we can do if we have this naming convention where we
always start off with the exact same name and then we have other different names after it, what we
can do is we can actually create a directory called car within our components file or components folder.
And then over here we can actually remove the car from these files so we can just say instead of hero,
we can say or instead of car hero, we can just say hero.
Let's just skip these changes.
It's fine.
We can just go ahead and actually move that in here now.
So I'm going to go ahead and just move that in there and we're going to do the exact same thing here.
Let's go ahead and just change that and we're going to move that in there.
And we're gonna say, okay, and now this is actually going to behave the exact same way.
The names is actually going to be exactly the same.
It's still going to be Car Hero, even though our file now is just hero.
And that's because what ends up happening in the component directory is if we want to specify a specific
file that is nested, we would have to append both names together.
So both names together, so be car hero and then car search bar.
That's pretty neat.
And if I were to go back here, of course, if I were to refresh, everything is working a okay.