So now that we are completely done with the home page, let us move on to the next page.
And that is going to be whenever we search for a particular city.
So let's say Ottawa.
In my case, I'm going to go ahead and click search.
It's going to take me to this page over here.
Now, this page is going to have the path of slash city slash Ottawa slash car.
Now, the reason why Ottawa is in green is because this over here is going to be dynamic and is going
to be dependent on whatever the user has decided to type.
So if they didn't type Ottawa, instead, they typed Toronto and we went ahead and looked at the route.
You can see now it's slash city slash Toronto slash car.
So you can see that this portion is always dynamic.
And so we need to figure out a way to add this dynamic path within our NOx application.
Now, slash city and also slash car are going to be static.
They're always going to be the same.
Now, another thing that I also want to note is that whenever we actually go to the car page and then
we change the make of the car.
So for example, let's say I change the make to I don't know what's a nice car, let's change it to
Toyota.
It's also going to change the path of our application.
So it's going to end up looking something like this.
So slash city slash auto slash car slash Toyota.
So this again, is going to be dynamic.
It could be Toyota, it could be Ferrari, it could be Bentley, it could be Hyundai.
However, however, it is also going to be optional.
So if we actually don't provide the make and we just have something like this, we should also have
the exact same page.
So whether we have the actual make as well or we don't have to make it is going to present us with the
exact same page, meaning that this is not only dynamic, it is also optional.
So we have to actually think about that when writing our rules.
Now, of course, we're not going to write any code for this.
We're going to just create a bunch of files and folders.
So I'm going to go over here and within the pages directory I'm going to create a bunch of other directories
that are going to follow this path over here.
So for example, I'm going to go over here and I'm going to create a directory.
Actually, let's just create a file for now and I'm going to call this city dot view.
We're going to delete this later, but just for demonstration purposes.
So I'm going to create this right over here, City View and I'm going to do a template div H one and
then city.
So go ahead and save that.
And now what ends up happening is if I go to my application and then I don't go to the slash index route,
instead I go to the slash city route.
You can see that I get a 404, which I was not expecting, and that's probably because I'm going to
have to go ahead and just close this terminal down and open it up again.
And that's probably what you have to do most of the time whenever you change your page's route.
So the hot reloading is not very smart.
In that case.
Let's just go ahead and just quickly do a little refresh here.
And there we go.
You can see now I actually have the city page.
So now, of course, I can go back to the home page.
I can go back to the slash city page.
And I went to this page over here, which doesn't exist.
So that's why we got this error.
But if I go back to just city on its own, I go and I see this so you can see that this is where we're
going to create all of our different routing rules within this page's directory.
We're going to create a bunch of folders and files to specify those rules.
So what I want to do is I want to have something like this.
I want to have and let me get rid of this for now.
I want to have something like Slash City, and then I want this part to be dynamic.
So whatever this city is.
So typically we would define that by doing something like this.
So slash city and then slash car and then I want to have the make, but again, I want this to be optional.
So how are we going to do that?
Well, let me go ahead and create another directory now.
And this time is going to be a folder, not a file.
A folder.
So I'm going to go over here.
I'm going to say city, and then I'm going to say or actually, well, we're going to say city in here.
We're going to create that one city folder.
And then within this city folder, we're going to create another folder and that's going to mark the
actual city.
So whether it's Ottawa, Toronto, Los Angeles, whatever.
Now, this is going to be a dynamic path.
So how do we specify something to be dynamic and not static like this over here?
Well, to specify something as dynamic, we wrap them in square braces.
So over here we're just going to say city are we're going to wrap it in square braces and city is just
going to be the variable name.
So over here now we got that.
So we've got city slash the dynamic city.
And now what I want to do is I want to create, well, another folder.
This time it's going to be car.
And then at the very end, this one's actually going to be a file.
So we can actually well, create our HTML elements.
So right over here we're going to say file and this one is going to be MC like so and it's going to
be dynamic.
So we're going to say make dot view like.
So.
However, not only do we want it to be dynamic, we want it to be optional.
Now, to make it dynamic and optional, very simply, we wrap it with double double square braces like
so.
So now we can go ahead and actually add that in.
And I'm going to go ahead and actually just remove this.
We do not need this anymore.
The city.
So right over here, we actually added this path.
So I'm going to go over here.
I'm just going to say template div, I'm going to say city and make for now and let's go.
We might have to refresh our page so now we can see we're getting a 500.
Let me just go ahead and just refresh our terminal.
And now what we're going to do is we're going to go to slash city and then slash whatever.
Doesn't matter what it is.
Well, let's just put something a little bit reasonable, like let's say Houston and then slash and
then core.
And that should take us to this HTML template over here, because again, this portion right here is
dynamic.
Now, we can also, if we wanted to go to slash city, slash Houston slash car, slash Toyota, and
that should also take us to the exact same page.
So let's go ahead and give this a quick shot.
So we're going to go over here.
We can see we're getting a 400 for page.
I'm going to go now to slash city slash Houston slash car.
And you can see we get city and make and now I'm going to go to slash city, slash Houston slash car
slash Toyota.
And today we get the exact same thing.
All right.
So we have created that path.
We have created it.
So now what we actually need to do is start populating it with components.
So let's actually do that in the next video.