Attached to this lecture.
You should have a class dot JSON file.
So what I want you to do is to go ahead and download it and then in your root directory, create a data
directory and put that cast JSON file within it.
Now the data directory is not a special directory.
It's not something that Knox looks for.
I just think it's a nice name to store our data.
So over here we have our castle JSON file and you can see that it is an array of objects and each object
has information about a particular car.
So it has the ID, the name, the price, the URL seats, miles features, and the description.
So what we're going to do is we're going to actually utilize this data right over here to render our
car cards right over here rather than have one static card.
So let's actually go ahead and do that.
Now, one thing that I would like to do in order to really organize everything is I'm going to create
a composable and this is going to be called use cars dot JS.
So let's go over here.
We're going to say const export use cars.
It's going to be an arrow function.
And over here what a very simply want to do is just import this data and just return it from this function.
So what we can do is at the very top of the file, we can just say import cars and then specify the
path to that directory.
So we can say dot, dot, slash to go to the root directory and then we can go to Stata.
And then over here, cars.
And then very simply now we can just say return cars like so.
However, one thing that we can actually do to optimize the import statement is because we are going
back to the root directory, we can actually kind of forego these dot dots and instead we can say at
and what this is going to do.
Once we say add, it's going to take us right to the root directory and then I'm going to say, okay,
from the root directory I want to go to data and then cars dot JSON.
Okay.
So that's pretty much all it is that we need to do.
And now I actually want to make use of this composable.
So let's go to the cards and over here let's create a script setup and I'm going to go ahead and just
grab this information.
So I'm going to say I want to get the cars from use cars.
And then what I'm going to do is I'm going to say V four over here and I'm going to say car in cars.
And we'll also have a key here and we'll say car dot ID And I think that's pretty much all it is that
we need.
And actually we have to also pass the props in.
So we'll just say car like so.
All right.
So now we should get three different cars and we don't.
And actually I think that's because over here inside of the make we're actually rendering the card and
not the cards.
So now if I were to save that, you can see we have three different cars.
But of course the data is static because we're not using the props.
So let's go back over here.
Let's go to the card and let's actually make use of those props.
So I'm going to say script, I'm going to say set up and over here I'm going to say const and I'll say
props is equal to define props, and we'll go ahead and just invoke that like so.
And over here, actually we'll just do an object and we'll just say car, and this is going to be an
object like so.
All right.
So now if I were to render car.
We should see all the information about that particular car.
There we go.
So let's go ahead and actually make this dynamic.
So for the source, I'm going to make this dynamic.
And over here, I'm just going to say car dot.
And I'll say, what did I call it here?
I believe I called it URL.
I'll just get rid of this.
Get rid of this, get rid of this, get rid of this or that.
So car dot URL.
So let's go over here.
Car URL.
That looks good to me.
And we'll say car dot and what I call this here car dot name for this.
And then over here, car description.
So say card dot descript shun.
And lastly, right over here we'll say car dot price.
Nice and easy stuff.
Okay, so now if I were to do a quick little refresh, you can see that everything is nice and dynamic.
So what I would like to do is actually now make these cards clickable.
So when I click on them, they actually go to the correct page.
So right over, we'll say right over here.
We might change this later on and I'll show you exactly why.
But right now we'll just add an add click.
And very simply, what we'll say is I want to navigate.
So navigate to and I want to navigate to and we'll add template literals here.
And where do we want to navigate?
Well, we want to navigate to slash car and then slash and then over here we will say car dot name and
then remember it's going to be dash and then the car dot ID.
All right.
So let's go ahead and quickly save that.
And now, if I were to click on this, you can see now I get taken to the actual car page.
So now that we got that dynamic, let's actually make this page over here dynamic rather than kind of
having rendering all of these static information.