In order to actually customize the data, we must search for the particular object that has the ID that
is present right over here.
So let's go ahead and actually extract that ID first and foremost.
So let's go to our pages directory.
So components, composable files right here, pages.
And I'm going to go to car, just go to this particular page right over here.
And you can see that we're actually already using this use route.
Now let's use route.
We're extracting the name from it, but we can also extract the I D And just to prove this to you,
I'm going to go ahead and right over here I'm just going to say route dot params dot ID, I remember
that's because we called it ID right here.
And I can see right here very faintly we have a two.
Okay, so we got the ID, but now what I want to do is I want to well search for that particular car
by its ID, so let's actually go ahead and create a computed value here and I'm going to say const and
I'll say car and I'll say that this is going to be equal to computed, computed.
And notice again that we can auto import computed.
And what we're going to do here in this function is very simply iterate over all of those cars and find
the one that has the ID that is within this route.
So to actually get access to those cars, we'll just say cars from or not from.
We'll just use the composable.
We'll just say use cars like.
So we're going to go ahead and invoke that.
And over here very simply, we'll just do is we'll return cars dot find and over here we'll say see.
And we shall return.
The C dot id is equal to.
We're going to do pass int because this ID even though it is really a number once we extracted from
the parameters, it will be a type of string.
So we have to parse enter into it.
And then over here we're going to say just root dot params, dot ID, All right.
That's all it is that we need to do.
And now what we can do here.
Is very simply just grab Oh, my goodness.
I'm just trying to grab whatever I give up.
Let's go over here.
I'm just going to grab the car here for now.
Let's go ahead and save that.
You can see we do indeed get the card details.
All right.
So let's actually go ahead and only render this if we have the car.
So let's just go here and just say if car and if we don't have the car, we can just render something
else.
And I'll show you exactly what we're going to do later on.
So now what we need to do is unfortunately pass in a lot of different props.
Now we can pass in the car prop to every single one.
That is completely fine.
And actually it's probably not the best idea being that, you know, some some of these components don't
really need all of the information.
So over here, for example, we can probably pass the whole car component into the car hero because
the car hero has a lot of information.
The the it has the image, it has the the name, the seats, the miles, the the price.
You know, it doesn't really matter if you pass in a little bit more information.
But for the other ones, we don't really need to pass everything.
We really just need to pass maybe the features.
So the car dot features like so.
And then over here.
We'll just pass a description.
So we'll say description.
And then over here we'll say car dot description.
So that's pretty much all it is that we need to pass in.
So now let's actually utilize these within the actual components themselves.
So let's go over here to components car.
Let's begin with the car hero and actually car detail hero is specifically what we're going to be using.
So let's go over here to script setup and we're going to say cons, props, and we'll say for this,
this is going to be defined props.
So define props.
And we'll just say car is going to be an object.
So again, over here now what we can do is very simply.
Extract this so it can be car dot URL, I believe it's called.
And now if I were to refresh this, you can see now we actually get the URL itself over here.
We can say car dot name over here, we can say car dot seats over here.
We can just talk about how many miles.
So a car dot miles.
And lastly here, car dot price.
All right.
So that's pretty much it for that.
So now let me just copy this.
Let's go to the attributes.
So the attributes and really all it is is a features array, so features and we can just say array for
this.
And just to show you what the features are, it's just an array of all of the different features of
the cars.
So what we can do now is we can go back to attributes and then right here we can just iterate over this
with av4, so we can just say V four.
And we can say feature in features.
And each feature is going to be unique, so we can use the actual feature itself as a key.
So you can just say feature.
And then over here we can say feature.
And let's just do a quick little refresh.
There we go.
So now we get all of those different features.
Last thing we need is the description.
So let's go here and let's go back to the attributes.
Copy this.
Paste that in there.
All right.
And this is just going to be a string, so let's just grab that and description like so.
So now I'm going to go ahead and just remove this and I'll just say description.
Description.
So I'm going to go and save that.
And there we go.
Now, you can see we have this description.
So this is looking pretty good.
We have made everything nice and dynamic.