So now let's go ahead and actually start populating this with all of the components that we need.
So, of course, we first need the nav bar.
So let's go over to our file.
And we have already well created that nav bar component so we can just now very simply just say nav
bar.
So we can say nav bar like so.
And now we should see our nav bar.
And now what we need to do is all the other HTML elements for our component.
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to go to the car's HTML.
You can see here where we have the car page.
I'm going to go ahead and just copy everything between the car page comments.
So let's go ahead and just copy that.
And we're going to go over here to make and we're going to go ahead and paste that in.
And there we go.
So now you can see we have this and we only have one card for now.
But later on, we'll render more.
Now, of course, what I want to also do is separate a lot of these things into their own component.
So let's begin with the car sidebar.
So over here, let's just grab everything in between the car sidebar and we're just going to go ahead
and just cut it out for now.
This is going to be this thing right over here.
And we're going to go to we're going to go over here.
We're going to go inside of the components directory, inside of car.
We're going to create a side bar view file and we're going to say templates and we're going to go ahead
and just paste that in there.
And then over here we're going to call car sidebar, very simple car side bar like.
So we can also remove these comments.
Okay, so that looks pretty good to me.
So I'm going to go ahead and just save that.
And now we have we still have everything looking the same.
Another thing that I do want to add now is two more components.
One for the car cards and then one for the car card, the actual card itself.
So the card cards is actually going to be a one div component.
So let's go over here and let's go over here.
We're going to say cards.
So this is plural.
And then over here we'll also create another one, which is going to be card singular.
All right, So let's go over here for the cards.
It's just one div element right over here, which is going to be v full.
So cards, we're just say template and then V full.
That's it.
And then for the cards, we're going to grab everything in here.
Just grab all of that.
Let's cut that out and let's just create a template and we're going to go ahead and paste that in there.
And then inside of the cards, we're going to render that just one card for now.
So we're going to say core card like so.
And so now over here, we can actually completely get rid of all of this and very simply just say car
and then card and then save that.
And theoretically, that should be it.
So you can see here that everything is working A-OK.