Now that we have made this nice and dynamic, we could potentially run into an error.
So let's say that a user decides to search for a car that has an ID that doesn't really exist in our
JSON file.
So I'm just going to put seven, seven, seven, seven, I'm going to press enter and you can see right
away we kind of get this blank screen.
And that's really because right over where is it?
Right over.
Where are we here?
Kind of forgot.
Right in the cards.
So in the cards right over here, we actually have a VRF and actually it's right over here.
So we have this VRF.
Now, if we didn't have this VRF, we're probably going to even run into a boatload of other issues.
So if I were to refresh, you can see here now we're getting a 500 error and it's actually going back
to that really nice error dot view file.
And you can see here that hey I cannot read property undefined of URL.
Now of course if I go back to a actual page you can see that everything is completely fine.
So what I want to do is when a user actually goes to an ID that is not of a car that exists in our JSON
file, I want to throw a custom error so we don't have that 500 error.
So right over here, what I'm going to do is I'm going to say if car value doesn't exist.
So if we can't find that particular car, the car is going to be null.
So I'm just going to say if it doesn't exist, what I'm going to do is I'm going to throw and then I'm
going to say throw, create error.
And this just allows us to create a nux error.
So I'm going to say over here, status code, I'm going to say 400 oh four and then for the message
I'm going to say, well, let's make this a nice dynamic message and I'm going to say car with ID,
I'll just say ID off and over here we'll just do rho dot params dot id and we'll say does not exist.
And so this is actually how we can go ahead and throw custom errors.
And so now any time I go to a page like this, you can see now I get a 404 and this time it's not a
404 page not found because this is actually a page that exists within our directory.
So this is an actual valid page.
However, we just can't find a car.
So it's still if 404 something was not found and now you can see the error message is a little bit different.
And let me just go ahead and actually capitalize this because it looks a little bit nicer so you can
see the powers of this.
So now what I can do is I can actually go ahead and go back and do whatever it is that I want.
However, once I create an error, that error is actually going to persist throughout the application.
So ideally, inside of the error view file, we actually clear that error.
And so we can actually do that by well, going over here and I can just say very simply, clear error.
So I can clear this error and also I can pass in an option, a redirect option to redirect me back to
the slash home page.
So that's going to clear that error.
So we don't have that error anymore.
So now let's go back over here.
I'll just search for auto and over here.
I'm just going to go and search for this portion and then I'm going to change this up to like five,
five, five.
You can see a car with this ID and we can actually go back and it clears the error itself.
So this is how we can throw custom errors within nux.