The last page that we need to work on is this page right over here.
So whenever I click on a particular car, I get redirected to the car details page, and this actually
has a very unique path within itself and this is the path that it has.
So it's going to be slash car.
This part is static.
It's always going to be slash car, but then it's going to be slash and then the name of the car.
In this case, it's Pausch.
And then we have a dash that is always going to be there.
It's static.
And then also we're going to have another dynamic ID So it's going to be the name of the car, which
is going to be dynamic a a static dash and then a dynamic ID and that's all within this same exact route.
So I actually highly suggest that you just try to figure out how to out how to do this on your own,
and then we'll proceed with this video.
So I'll give you a quick chance to pause the video.
Go ahead and pause it.
I assume at this point you have paused it and tried.
So let's go ahead and show you exactly how to do it.
So we're going to go over here and now we're going to go to the pages directory.
So remember, the static part is going to be slash car.
So we're going to create a new folder called Car.
And then within here it's going to be slash car and then slash that actual car and then dash ID.
So over here, what we're going to do is we're going to create a new file and to specify that this is
going to be dynamic.
We're going to say square braces name.
And then right after the Square braces, we're going to add a dash.
Then we're going to add another set of square braces.
And that's going to be the ID dot view.
And that's exactly how we do it.
Very, very simple stuff.
And you can see how powerful and easy this is becoming.
So over here we can create a template.
And now let's actually go ahead and create everything it is that we need.
So we need the nav bar.
So let's go over here.
Let's add the nav bar, let's go ahead and save that.
And now I'm going to go to the car detail page and I'm just going to copy everything within here.
So let's just copy everything here and we'll separate them into components in a moment.
So let's go over here.
Let's go to the car detail page.
Go ahead and save that and let's see if this is working A-OK now.
So I'm going to go to slash car and then slash and I'm going to say I'm going to say slash Toyota doesn't
really matter and then slash five.
And if I enter that, you can see we actually get the page.
So it does indeed work.
Now, let's go ahead and quickly separate them into their own separate components.
So let's go over here, the car hero itself.
So we're going to go ahead and grab this and let's go here.
Actually.
Where does this end?
Ends right here.
That should be okay.
Sorry for the confusion.
There's a dive right here that starts right here.
So this actually should be.
This should end right here.
So sorry for the confusion, everybody.
And honestly, I don't even think we need that div.
We can probably just remove it, but we'll just leave it just for for the sake of leaving it.
So let's go ahead over here and we'll just grab this car hero and let's go over here and let's create
another component.
Now the issue is we already have a hero component.
So what we can do now is we can just say, add another directory, we can call this details.
So car detail.
And then over here we can just say Hero dot view and I'm going to go over here, just add a template
and add all of that HTML within there.
And then over here I can just say car and then it's detail and then hero.
And if I were to go ahead and render that and refresh, you can see I still get the exact same thing.
And I believe I can probably get rid of this div as well as this.
So let's go ahead and do that.
Let's go ahead and refresh.
Yeah, everything is looking good.
Okay, so now let's go to the attributes.
So let's go here.
We're going to go ahead and cut that out.
And we're also going to put that in the details directory.
We're going to say attributes dot view and let's create a template.
Go ahead and create that.
And then over here we're going to say.
Just right below this, we're going to say car detail, attributes, attributes.
So now we can go ahead and get rid of these comments.
And now let's do the description as well.
So we're going to go here, grab that description.
Let's go back over here.
We'll say description.
Dot view.
Go ahead and create a template for this template.
Paste that in there.
Save that.
And of course, the contact as well is the last thing that we need.
So let's grab that contact and let's go back up here.
We'll say contact dot view template and we'll say paste that in there.
All right.
So that's pretty much it.
So now we can just say car detail and we'll say description and then car detail contact.
There we go.
Looking good.
So we have pretty much created all of our different pages as well as the components for them.
We should be extremely happy at this point.