The error that we have just created is actually known as a server side error, and that might not make
all too much sense to you if you don't understand exactly how web content is rendered onto the browser.
So what we're going to do is a little quick aside break from the code, and we're going to go through
some really important concepts that you really, really have to understand and master if you want to
master Nux three.
So right now we have a browser that is exactly what we are looking at right now.
Now this could be either Google Chrome, Firefox Safari doesn't really matter.
It is a browser.
Now let's say that we go to a particular website airbnb.com.
Amazon.com doesn't really matter.
It could also be local host 3000.
That is a website.
So we go to that particular website.
What do we expect?
Well, we expect content, of course, so we expect content to be rendered onto the screen.
So we're expecting HTML, we're expecting CSS.
We're also expecting JavaScript to make the website nice and interactive.
Now, the million dollar question is how in the world does the HTML and the CSS and the JavaScript that
we need will get to the browser because at some point, at some point it's going to be completely empty.
But then we're going to make a request and then we're going to want to get that data, that HTML, CSS
files, etc..
So how do we do that?
Well, we do that with a server.
So with any website, it is always going to have a development server.
So if we go to Airbnb somewhere hosted in the cloud, probably in AWS, there is a web development server
and even our NUX applications.
Whenever we do NPM run dev, it spins up a development server.
I'm sorry, if you go to airbnb.com, it's not going to be a development server, it's going to be an
actual server web server that is hosted on us.
But nonetheless there is always a server.
Now the way that the browser and the server interact with one another is going to dictate which type
of rendering style that will we eventually choose.
So there's two different types of rendering styles.
There is server side rendering and then there's client side rendering.
So let's quickly discuss server side rendering.
So let's say that we go to localhost 3000, so we go to localhost 3000.
What ends up happening is the client makes a request to the browser, to the server right over here.
So the browser makes a request to the server and the server gives you everything that you need in order
to render that particular page.
Because right now we're on the slash page.
So it gives you the home page HTML, which has everything which has the hero content, also gives you
the CSS and it also gives you the JavaScript.
So just goes ahead and pretty much just gives you everything right off the bat and the browser just
grabs it and renders it.
Now why is this server side rendering?
Well, because really the server is doing all of the work.
It is just creating.
The HTML file is creating the CSS file, it's creating the JavaScript file, and it's just giving it
to the client, the browser, and the client is just, well, taking it and just rendering it.
That's why this is server side rendering.
Now let's say that we decide to go to a different page.
Well, if we go to a different page, then the client is going to go ahead and make another request
to the web server.
And the web server is going to pretty much do the exact same thing, but for this page instead.
So now it's going to give us the cars, start HTML, the cars, CSS, the cars, start JavaScript,
and now we have all of the content that we need.
So I hope that makes sense.
So for each particular page, we're making a request, we're getting data back.
So now let's talk about client side rendering, and this one might be a little bit more confusing,
but hopefully I can explain it in a way where it's not as confusing.
So let's say I go to local host 3000, so I go to this particular website.
The client, like with server side rendering, is going to make a request to the web server, but the
web server, instead of actually giving you the HTML for that particular page as well as the CSS as
well as the JavaScript initially, it just gives you an empty HTML file and it's not really empty.
There's just like the basic body as well as the head, but there's really nothing in there.
It's just kind of completely empty and add to the browser.
It's just going to be completely empty because there's really nothing in the body.
So it gives you this empty HTML file and you might be thinking, why in the world would it do this?
This doesn't really make all too much sense.
Well, right afterwards, right after it sends you the HTML file, it sends you a JavaScript.
Bundle for the whole application.
It doesn't matter what page it is, it just gives you the JavaScript bundle for all of the application.
The client gets it, and then the client starts to parse that JavaScript bundle.
And that JavaScript bundle contains all of the information about the HTML, the CSS, and all of the
logic that needs to be rendered for a particular page.
So the client is going to start parsing it.
And then once it starts parsing it, it's going to start rendering and creating HTML elements.
So eventually at the end of the day, we achieve the exact same thing.
But how we got there is a little bit different.
Now, why is this called client side rendering?
Well, as you can imagine, the client is the one that's going to be doing all the hard work.
It's parsing the JavaScript and it's going ahead and it's rendering all of the HTML elements.
Now, one thing that is really nice about client side rendering is now that we have this JavaScript
bundle, if we go to a different page, we don't have to make another request to the server.
We already have all of the logic inside of the client.
So what we can do is, well, the client is going to go ahead and parse that JavaScript and it's just
going to kind of re render components.
It's going to remove a component and then add another component.
And so it's going to kind of give the illusion of a multi page application.
But in reality it's really just one HTML file that is just changing its HTML consistently.
But again, the nice part is, is we don't have to make a request back to the server and get the data
back.
So let's do a quick little refresher.
So server side rendering is when of course we make the request and we get everything right back.
Now, of course there's pros and cons to each approach, so let's talk about some of the pros.
So one of the biggest pro is that it renders all of the HTML elements right away, which is awesome
for SEO.
Obviously, if we want to have search engine optimization, we want to make sure that our application
is at the very top of search engines.
We want to have as much keywords as possible, as much HTML elements as possible.
And so this is great for SEO and it's also has a faster initial render because it doesn't have to wait
for to parse all of this JavaScript.
It kind of just gets it right away.
Now, of course, it also has quite a bit of cons.
So one major, major, major con is that, well, you know, we are making multiple requests to the
server.
We're consistently making these requests to the server.
So if you go to another page, we make another request, we go to another page, we make another request
which actually causes, you know, slower navigation across pages.
So even though the initial render is fast and it's going to be faster than client side rendering is
going to be slower to navigate across pages because we have to make a request and get the response back.
And of course, well, making requests continuously is expensive.
You know, making requests is not going to be free whenever we're hosting a larger application.
So now let's talk about client side rendering.
So client side rendering, one huge benefit is it really only hits the server just once so we don't
have to hit it multiple different times.
And so it's not expensive at all.
We just get everything all at once.
And also it causes smoother and faster navigation.
So because we're not hitting the server when we navigate and we're just, you know, just removing components
and re rendering different HTML elements, it's a lot smoother and faster.
However, of course, it has a slower initial render, which is true because, well, it is.
We have to parse that JavaScript.
And also it's terrible for SEO because we'll remember we're only getting that empty HTML file and we're
going to actually render that HTML file.
And then the SEO, the search engines are going to go ahead and take a look at that and be like, Oh,
okay, well, there's nothing there, so I'm not going to promote this because there's really no content
there.
So it's not really all to great for SEO.
So now that we have an understanding of server side rendering and client side rendering, that begs
the question what is Nux, What does Nux use?
Does it use server side or does it use client side?
Well, the answer is neither, but both.
So let me explain.
So it actually kind of uses something known as universal rendering and it is kind of a combination of
both client side as well as server side rendering and it kind of takes the best of both worlds and it
kind of omits the cons.
So let me kind of explain exactly how universal rendering works.
So let's say over here we have our our browser and we go to local host 3000.
So exactly like server side rendering.
We're going to go ahead and make a request to our server and our server is going to return everything
right back.
So this is going to be obviously awesome for the initial load and it's also going to be terrific for.
CEO, but it doesn't stop there.
So as soon as let's say we're playing around with the page, the server is going to go ahead and kind
of in the background, it's going to send us the JavaScript bundle and the JavaScript bundle is going
to go ahead.
And this is a very common term in Nux.
It's going to hydrate our application.
So it's just going to kind of make everything functional.
And then let's say I want to move to a different page, so I want to move to a different page because
now we have that JavaScript bundle and we're hydrated.
We don't have to make that request again, so we don't have to make that request to the server.
Again, we're just going to move around with the HTML, just like we have our client side rendering.
So you can see now we have the effects of both server side rendering and client side rendering.
We have the pros of them without the cons.
So this is kind of a really important concept to understand, is that, you know, in some cases we
are going to be server side rendering and in other cases we're going to be client side rendering.
Now, why is this right over here a server side error?
Well, let's go back to our page over here.
And this this really only occurs when we go directly to a particular path.
So let's go over here to slash.
We're going to slash core and we write in an ID that just doesn't exist.
And so we just say enter, and this is going to be the initial load.
And so this is going to be a server side error.
So we we requested to go directly to this page and of course this is going to be the initial load kind
of like this over here.
And we're going to get our HTML, CSS, our JavaScript, and of course over here this is going to cause
this server side error.
Now there's obviously different types of errors, like client side errors, which we're going to see
in the next section.