Now that we have created all of our different pages, I want to have the ability to navigate within
these pages, within the actual application itself, and not have to well redirect to whatever page
I want to go to.
So, for example, if I want to go to that slash city slash dynamic city name over here, if I want
to go to this page, what I don't want to do is actually have to type that into the URL itself.
What I want to do is I want to just say auto search and have it move me there itself.
Another thing that I would like is to have this nav bar be functional.
So whenever I click on this, I would very much like it for it to go back to the home page.
So let's actually begin with the naff bar, because that's, that's actually the simplest thing that
we can do right now.
So the nav bar.
Very simply, whenever we click on this, I just want it to go back to the slash root, the home page.
And what we can do to do that is we can go to our nav bar components.
So let's go to our nav bar components right over here.
And what we can do here is we can actually make the rough slash so we can make it slash h ref.
And now when I go over here, you can see that it takes me back to this page.
However, just like in view, where when we ever add an H ref, instead of adding a view link or a view
a route or link, instead of using that, what it's going to do is it's going to refresh our page,
which is not that great.
So instead what we're going to do is we're going to use a built in Nux component called Nux link.
So Nux link right over here.
And that's going to allow us to navigate across pages but not have to refresh our page every time.
And it does start with something called universal rendering, which we'll talk about a little bit later.
So we're going to change the ref from not being a ref, but instead to two.
And notice that we didn't have to import this in.
Again, this is something that was auto imported.
So now if I go ahead and actually save this and let me go to another page now, let's go to this page
and then if I go over here, you can see it got redirected back to this page, which is terrific.