We got the nod for working.
But now I want to get this search bar working over here.
And for this search bar, we can't really use a nux link because we need to programmatically change
the path.
So let's go to our search bar.
So let's go over here to car and we're going to go to search bar and over here this is where we're going
to dynamically change the path itself.
So we're going to go and we're going to have to utilize a script tag.
So we're going to say script and we're going to say setup.
So script set up like so.
And how do we typically do this?
Well, we typically do this by first adding a V model.
So we can go over here, we can add a V model, we can call this city.
And then over here we can create a constant city is equal to ref, so we can actually store the value.
Now notice we don't have to import ref in again, this is something that is auto imported.
So that's the very first thing that we're going to do.
And then typically what we're going to do is we're going to go ahead and just say cost and then we're
going to get rotor from the use rotor composable.
And then what we're going to do is whenever we click this button right here, let's go ahead and just
say add click, let's just say handle search, create a function called handle search here so we can
say const, handle search.
And over here, what we can very simply do is just say rotor.
So rotor dot push and then we can push in the path that we want.
So over here, what is it?
The path that we want, what we want to go to slash city.
And then in this case it's going to be slash city dot value.
And then over here we're going to say slash car.
Now there's going to be no make.
So we're not going to add that part.
And that's pretty much actually all it is that we need to do to get that to work.
So if I were to say auto in here and say search, you can see that that does indeed work and take me
to where I need to be.
Okay, so this is good.
However, this actually isn't that necessary with Knox.
So Knox actually makes this a little bit simpler.
So instead of using the use route or composable to go ahead and actually add this path, instead, we
can actually kind of completely get rid of this used road or composable and instead use the navigate
to function.
That again, is going to be auto imported for us.
So I'm going to go ahead and just cut this out and just paste it right in here inside of the navigate
to function.
And now I'm going to do just a quick little refresh here.
Let's change this to, let's say, Asia to Los Angeles.
And if I go ahead and click search, you can see now it has navigated me back to Los Angeles.
So that is great and that is amazing.
Now there is one potential issue and this doesn't really relate to Nux.
I can go ahead at this point and just search and it's going to take me to the slash city and let me
just zoom in here slash city slash slash and then car and that's because the city is empty.
So one thing that we can also do just as a quick precaution is check if the city is indeed is indeed
not empty.
So what we can do here is we can say if the city dot value is empty, then what we can do is we can
return early.
And another thing that we can also do, just so we can show some sort of user feedback, is we can create
another piece of state.
And I can just say city error.
And for now I'm going to say city error is false.
And over here I'm just going to say return city error.
Dot value is equal to true.
And now what we can do here is we can go to this input over here and we can add a dynamic class.
So we can say class and we can say if we have a city error, then what we want to do is we want to render
a border that is red.
So we can say here, actually let's go to Tailwind, just to just to show you exactly how we do this.
So we're going to go over here and we're going to just search for border and we're going to say border
color, for example, and I want a red border.
So let's just scroll all the way over here.
So kind of a border like this.
So this is the class that we're going to use, which is going to be border red and 500.
So border red, 500 like so.
And also we need to add a border.
So I believe we also add this class over here and then we'll just say else, then add nothing at all.
So let's go ahead and just quickly just see if that works.
Let's go back home.
Let's zoom out.
Let's go to Tur.
Oh, it's actually not add anything.
And there we go.
You can see we get this kind of red state.
I know it's kind of ugly right over here.
That's completely fine.
Who cares?
But you can see that we actually get this red color, which is amazing.
But now if I go to Toronto or whatever you can see now, and if you go back, everything is completely
fine.