So now that we understand the difference between server side as well as client side rendering, let's
take a look at a potential client side error that we might potentially face whenever we're dealing with
NOx three.
Now, in order to actually see this error, I actually want to make this sidebar functional.
And specifically, let's just focus in on the location right over here.
So let's go to our sidebar component and you can see in the sidebar component that we have this div
element that contains other HTML elements.
And this array over here is kind of just our modal that is going to appear whenever we click on the
actual city that we're currently in.
And I'm going to zoom in here just for you guys.
So let's just make this a little bit functional.
This is going to be just a little bit of JS over here.
So we're going to go here just or maybe not.
JS Well, JavaScript and just regular view.
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to create a piece of state, I'm going to call this const Modal,
and I'm going to say Ref, and I'm going to make this an object and I'm going to say, make an initially
false and over here, location false.
And then over here we're going to say price false.
So just a quick reminder, We have three different categories.
And for now, I'm going to make everything false, which means that everything all the models are not
going to be rendered.
And now if you do want to render, say, the location modal, then this is going to all change to true.
So let's go over here and let's only render this false out of V if we'll just say V, if we're only
going to render this if well, modal dot and we'll say dot in this case location.
So we only want to render that if this is true.
And in this case, obviously it's not true.
Well, when do we want to make it true?
Well, of course we want to make it true.
Whenever we well, click on, we're going to say this right over here.
So whenever we click on this H three, we want to go ahead and actually make that true.
So let's go.
And I'm going to say adds Click.
And I'm going to create a function here.
I'm going to say update modal, update to modal.
I'm going to pass in a key called location just so we can kind of reuse this function throughout our
app.
So I'm going to go over here and I'm going to go here and I'm just going to say const and I'll say update
modal, and that's going to be a function that's going to take in key, which is just going to be what
either make location or price.
And very simply, all we're going to do here is we're going to say modal dot value of that particular
key.
I want to change it to what it's not currently.
So in essence, I'm just going to say bank and then a modal dot value, dot key.
So very simple stuff.
So now if I were to click on this.
You can see we get the moral or we don't get the moral.
Okay, so that's just very simple.
But now I want the ability to actually change the city.
So let's say I go ahead and change it to Ottawa.
I want to be able to click apply, and then I want it to actually change the route.
So instead of being slash car, it's going to be slash car slash Ottawa.
So let's go ahead and actually do that.
Sorry, It's going to be slash city slash Ottawa slash car.
So I'm going to go over here and I'm going to create a new function.
I'm going to say on change location and I'm going to go over here and it's going to be a very simple
function.
I'm going to go ahead and actually close the modal again so I can just call update modal for location,
because that's going to go ahead and close it for me.
And then what I'm going to do is I'm going to say navigate to a very specifically, I just want to navigate
to slash city and then I'm going to say slash and then dollar sign.
And of course, what we're going to need to do is actually store the input itself.
So let's just say Con city is equal to ref and let's have a V model over here in this input.
So we'll say the model now we'll say City Dot or just say the model city like so.
And then over here we can just say city dot value and then we'll say slash car.
And then we might also have a make.
So we need to make sure that we add that to make so we can just say route dot params dot make.
Now if there isn't a make, then it's just going to be completely empty.
So it's going to be what it was before.
Now of course, in order to actually utilize route, we have to define it.
So we're going to say cost route is equal to use route and we're going to go ahead and invoke that.
So this is looking pretty good.
One little modification I would like to do is I want to say if city dot value, if that is not defined.
So it's just completely empty.
I don't want to navigate.
I just want to return.
And I also don't even want to close the modal.
I just want to return early.
Okay.
So that should pretty much be it.
And actually one other thing is, at the very bottom, we're going to go ahead and actually empty this
out.
So that should work theoretically.
So if I were to go ahead and change this to, let's say, Ottawa.
And apply.
Let me do just a little refresh here.
I'm going to go to of course, it's not going to work because we're not using this function.
So let's use this function and the apply button.
So I'm going to say at click.
And then over here we're going to call that function.
So now let's just say Ottawa, I'm going to go ahead and apply.
Now you can see it says City Ottawa slash car, which is good.
Now, another thing that's not all too great is this right over here?
You can see that this is hard coded as Toronto.
So I want to of course, we'll make it not hard coded.
So let's go over here and I'm going to change this to be the route dot params and then dot city so it
can actually be the actual city itself.
So over here now I can see it's Ottawa and if I were to change this to Houston, I can see that it is
now Houston.
Okay, so that's looking good.
Now let's say, let's say a user is not good.
You know, user is not being a really good user and he's just putting some gibberish and specifically
they're putting in a number.
Then what I want to do in this case is I want to throw an error saying that this is not a valid city.
So let's actually go ahead and do that in the next section.