In this video.
What I want to do is focus in on this page right over here.
So right now, the path is slash city slash Ottawa slash car.
Now, let's quickly talk about exactly which portion of this page is going to change the most whenever
we change the path.
Well, this sidebar is going to change very, very little.
It's still going to have the location to make the price.
But maybe these values are going to be different and they're just going to be extracted from the route
itself.
So this is going to change very, very little.
However, it's going to be this portion that changes dramatically.
So if I change it from Ottawa to Toronto, we're going to have a bunch of different cars that exist
in Toronto rather than Ottawa.
If I change it from Toyota to Volvo, then we're only going to show Volvo cars.
So I think what we need to do is change our routing structure so that this portion right over here that
changes the most is actually going to be a nested route.
So let me go ahead and quickly try to explain this by well, going through it.
So right over here, we're going to go to our city.
And remember, we have the city slash dynamic city slash car and then make now within this city directory,
I'm going to create another file and I'm going to call this car dot view.
So car view like so.
And this is actually going to conflict with the car view that we have over here, because then this
is going to be slash city slash well the dynamic city slash car and then and this should be and then
over here we have the slash car dot view.
And then over here we also have slash city slash dynamic city and then slash car.
And we also have an optional make.
So it's going to conflict and we'll fix that confliction a little bit later.
So we're going to add a template here and we're pretty much going to add exactly what we had.
But this time inside of this car dot view file.
So I'm going to go ahead, add the nav bar, I'm going to add the div, we're going to add the car,
car side bar, but now we're going to do so.
Now what we're going to do is right over here, instead of actually rendering the car cards, what we're
going to do is we're going to render a nux page.
So a nux page like so.
And then over here within our make, we're going to remove all of this stuff.
So we're going to remove the nav bar.
So let's remove the nav bar, we're going to remove this some, remove that, let's remove this, We're
going to literally keep, we're going to remove everything except for the car card and maybe have a
div right here.
So that div.
So that's, that's what we're going to do.
And so what's going to happen now is we're going to go to it's going to render the car view file and
then we're going to have this nux page and now any other path that we have in there.
So right now we're at the slash car and any other path over here that we have is going to actually render
right here inside of this Nux page.
So initially the root nux page is going to render all of our different pages, but now any other path
that is after car is going to be rendered in this nux page because we have this nested route.
Now in this case we actually do have a slash car slash make which is dynamic and optional and so it's
going to go ahead and render this.
So eventually we're going to actually achieve the exact same thing.
So let me just go ahead and prove this to you by doing a little quick refresh and tada, you can see
we still have our make and we still have our car.
And just to kind of really make this as clear as possible, I'm going to go ahead and I'm going to remove
this nux page.
And now you can see that that component is completely gone.
So if I were to add it back, it is back.
And now let me just go ahead and actually just rename this for now to like make but static.
And so now if I go to slash whatever, it's not going to know what that page is.
However, if I go to slash make, it's going to know what that page is and it's going to render that.
And if I go ahead and add another page and I'll just say Hello dot view and I'm just going to say template
div and then H one hello, whatever.
And now if I go to Slash Hello, you can see I'm going to have to refresh the page here, unfortunately,
or maybe refresh it.
I think it should work.
Nope, does not.
So let's go over here.
Let's refresh the whole thing.
It's kind of unfortunate that it makes me refreshed the whole time because I'm going to have to delete
those later.
But now I hope you guys can understand if I go to slash scar slash Hello as it loads up.
Just play with the circle.
You can see now we get this over here.
So if I change this back to make sure we get that.
All right?
So I hope that it is nice and clear.
So I'm going to go ahead and just delete this for now.
We do not need that.
So we remove the trash and we're going to rename this back to what it was before.
So I hope you guys get the point of nested components.