The last thing that I would like to do in this section is change the titles of each particular page.
So if you were to look at your tabs right now, you can see we get this really ugly title Local host
3002 slash city slash auto slash car slash make.
Not a very pretty title and same over here you know nothing about this is pretty at all So I want to
go ahead and actually change the titles and it is going to be remarkably easy to do with NOx three.
So let's go over here and I'm going to go to the let's go to rates over here.
Let's go to our very first page.
And I want to change the title so that as soon as you go to the home page, it should say car trader.
So over here, what we're going to do is we're going to create a script tag.
We're going to say setup.
Are we going to use a built in NOx composable called use head?
We're going to go ahead and invoke this and then we're going to pass in a bunch of options.
Specifically, we're going to pass in the title option.
And then over here we're going to say car trader like so.
And that's actually all it is that we need to do.
So now, if you look at your actual tab over here, you can see that it says car trader rather than
localhost 3000.
So now let's go ahead and actually do the exact same thing over here.
So I'm going to go to Ottawa and I am going to search over here and we're not getting anything.
And there we go.
I'm not sure why that was happening.
Let's go back here.
Let's search Ottawa.
There we go.
So it was just a little glitch there.
And I actually want to change this so that well, what do we have over here?
So if I go to Toronto, what I want it to have, I want it to say cars in Ottawa.
So cars in Ottawa, that's what I wanted to say.
So let's go over here to that particular page, which is going to be this page right here.
So we're going to go to this page and we're going to go.
Over here.
Are we going to say script setup?
And we're going to go ahead and just say use head.
And we're going to say title and this is going to be a dynamic title.
So we're going to say cars and then in and then auto, well, we're going to grab it from the root.
So we're going to say const root is equal to use root like so.
And we're going to say cars in and then we're going to say root.
And to actually grab the city, we're going to say slash params and then slash city, because that's
what we called it here city, the variable name.
And we're also going to capitalize this in case it's not capitalized, we're going to say dot two and
then we're going to say oh two.
Okay, So we can't necessarily there's no function to capitalize this.
So this is what we're going to do.
We're going to do this on the fly here.
We're going to say JavaScript.
Gonna say JavaScript function to capitalize, to capitalize, or we're just going to say that.
Okay, let's see if that works.
So we're going to go to Stack Overflow.
And.
All right.
This is going to capitalize.
So that's going to capitalize the first letter.
Not really what I want here.
I wanted to capitalize everything.
So capitalize.
Let's just say title.
Convert string to tidal case with JavaScript.
All right.
So let's see here.
Okay.
This looks like a good solution.
So we'll just say to Title case, just grab this function over here and I am going to just put this
function right here and we're going to say.
We're just going to wrap this with two title case to title case.
I'm going to go ahead and add that in there.
Okay.
So now we should see.
If I were to go back here.
You see, we get cars in Ottawa.
But actually I want to make this a little bit more dynamic.
So if I actually add the make instead of having cars, I want to say something like Buicks in Ottawa.
So if I add Buicks, it should say Buicks in Ottawa.
So this actually is going to be pretty easy as well.
So we're just going to go over here and we're just going to say dollar sign.
And this time we need to check if the route dot params dot MC is even there.
So if we have the MC itself, then what we want to do is we want to say to title case and actually pass
in the route dot params dot.
Make else.
What we want to do is we'll just say cars, just generic cars.
All right.
So that's pretty much all it is that we need to do.
So I'm just going to kind of let me zoom out of here a bit so you can really see that zoom out so you
can kind of see the whole thing.
And actually if I save, you can see that auto saved it.
So this is how it should look.
So now you can see it says cars and auto.
But if I go to slash Buicks, it says Buicks in auto or Buick in Ottawa, plural.
Okay, So this is great.
And now the last thing that I want to do is whenever I click on a particular a particular car, it should
take me to the slash car and then slash whatever, let's say was Buick and then five.
So this is just going to be the actual name of the car itself.
So let's go over here and we're going to also use the use head for this.
So what does this say script set up?
And we'll say use head and title.
And this one, we're going to say, let's go ahead and just say const root.
Is equal to use route.
And then over here, we're just going to say the name of the car itself.
So it's just going to be routes, dot params, dot and params dot.
And then the the actual name of the car, which is the name.
Now of course I'm going to want to title case this as well.
So what we're going to do is we're going to grab this function and what we'll think of we'll have a
better way if actually putting this function in one place instead of having it in just, you know,
copying and pasting it throughout components.
But for now, we'll just do that.
So we're going to go over here and we'll just title case this and now you can say Buick right over here.
Okay, So this is looking pretty, pretty good.
And that actually concludes the section on file base routing.