All right, everybody, welcome to a brand new section.
And in this section, we're going to mainly focus in on cleaning up our code a little bit.
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to begin with looking into all of the different view files that
pertain to our pages.
So let's go into our pages directory.
And what I did is I opened up the indexed view, which is the home page.
I then opened up the car view, which is going to be the car listing page.
And then I opened up this page over here, the name Dash ID dot view, which is actually the car itself.
And I want to kind of just explore the code at this point.
So let's begin with the indexed view, and I want to focus in on the HTML, not the script tag.
So let's go over here.
So we have the template, we have the div, and over here we have our nav bar component and then we
have our car hero.
So let's actually look at a common pattern when we go to the car out view.
So we have our template, we have our div and then we have our nav bar at the very top and then we have
our div that's going to contain all of the HTML that pertains to this page.
Now if I go back over here, you can see the exact same thing.
We have our nav bar and then we have a div that contains all of the different components that live inside
of this page.
So what are we noticing here?
We're noticing kind of a common pattern.
So throughout these three pages we always render the nav bar component and importantly, very importantly,
we always render it in the exact same position.
So it's always at the very top.
So you can see here the nav bar component is at the very top, the nav bar component is at the very
top and the nav bar is component that is at the very top.
And most likely if we add more and more pages, we're going to want to have that nav bar component be
at the very top.
And of course we are going to want to render it.
So why wouldn't it be nice if we can somehow abstract this away, if somehow we don't have to actually
render the nav bar for every single page we can just have nux figure out that I want to have a nav bar
for every single page and I want it to be located at the very top of the page.
So how can we do that?
Well, we can actually do that with something known as layouts.
So layouts allow us to lay out our page and we can also have a default layout.
And I think it will make a lot more sense once we actually go ahead and code out our very first layout.
So layouts only work inside of a layout directory.
So let's go ahead and create directory and it has to be called layouts.
And as you can imagine, it's going to be very similar reason as to why this has to be called component
and why this has to be called pages.
Knox is going to understand that the view files inside of this layouts directory are layouts, and it's
going to do some magic behind the scenes.
So let's go ahead over here and we're going to do layouts and we're going to create a new file.
Now, typically, we don't really care what we call the file.
I guess in the pages we do care depending on the path.
But over here, this actually matters a lot.
We have to call it default dot view to define a default layout that is going to exist for every single
page in our application.
So let's go ahead and create that page and this is just going to be a regular well view file.
So we're going to have a template, a div.
And then what I'm going to do is I'm going to define at the very top, I always want to render the nav
bar.
And then what I'm going to do is I'm going to define the slot component.
Now this isn't any nux specific component.
This is something that we already see in Vue three.
It is is in essence what this is, is all of the HTML that is going to be housed right over here inside
of these specific files.
So right now the slot component would be all of this HTML right over here.
Similarly, the slot component will be this over here.
So now what we're saying is, Hey, I want the nav bar and I want everything all the other HTML that's
rendered over here.
So let's go ahead and actually save those.
And in order to actually get this to work, we need to go over here to the app dot view and we need
to wrap this with a nux layout.
Just saying that hey, I want my nux page to use the Knox layout.
So let's go over here.
And right away we actually notice something interesting.
We have two nav bars and then we have our hero right over here.
And if I were to click on let's say Toronto now where to go search, you can see again two nav bars
and we.
Have our research and if I were to click on a specific car.
Oh, yeah.
We didn't make this clickable yet.
Yeah, that's later on.
Don't worry.
Uh, let's go over here.
We'll say car and we'll just go to Jeep one.
And over here you can see we have two nav bars, and this actually makes sense.
So what this is doing is it's taking this default layout.
And where is that?
It's taking this default layout and it's applying it to every single page.
So what it's doing is it's adding this nav bar and then it's adding all of the HTML that is within the
page, and that also includes an additional nav bar.
So the whole point of adding the layout is so we can remove the need of adding that additional nav bar.
So I'm going to go ahead and actually do that so we don't have those double nav bars.
So I'm going to go ahead and remove those double nav bars and let's go over here.
And we're going to go ahead and remove that.
And there we go.
So now you can see we have pretty much drastically cleaned up our code.
And you can imagine if our Linux application is getting huge.
Maybe we have 100 different pages now.
We don't have to add that nav bar component at the very top every single time.