So we learned about layouts, which is great.
You can see it's a really nice way to clean up our code.
However, right now I'm going to go ahead and just focus in on some of these pages over here.
So let's first look at this page over here.
So we have our nav bar and we also have this hero.
And then let's go to this page right here.
Now, you can see we have the nav bar, but you can see that all of the content, no matter how much
content that we have, is always going to be confined from right over here to right over here.
So right here to right here.
And it's not going to spend the entire width of our screen.
And if I were to go to let's say I'm going to go let's just pick a car here.
So slash, slash car and then we're going to say Jeep one.
You can see here, this is the exact same thing.
So it's always going to span right over here.
It's not going to we're always going to have these white spaces and it's going to span kind of right
in the middle.
And this is actually done by having this div element right here.
So this div has all of the tailwind classes that are needed to have that stylistic effect.
And the only really exist in right now two of our pages, our main page doesn't have this exact div,
this exact div element.
Now in cases where we have maybe some pages, you know, a group of pages that follow a particular layout,
but others that don't, we obviously don't want to have a default layout for all of them, but instead
what we want to do is we want to have a custom layout and then apply that custom layout to those group
of pages.
So again, in our case, these two pages have this div right over here and I think it would be nice
to kind of abstract it into a layout.
So again, what we're going to need to do is define a custom layout and let's go ahead and do that.
So custom layout can be called whatever it is that we want and call them banana dot view, whatever
dot view.
I'm just going to go ahead and just call them custom dot view just to kind of kind of ensure in your
mind that this is a custom layout.
I'm going to go ahead and just define the div, the template, and then I am going to go and grab this
div right here.
So go ahead and just grab that.
I'm going to go ahead and paste it in here.
So I'm going to go ahead and paste it in here and let's add the closing div as well.
So closing div like so and so over here is where I'm going to house the slot.
So over here is where I'm going to house the slot like so.
So now what I want to do is I want to actually utilize this custom layout within these two pages.
So what we're going to need to do is actually override the default layout.
And to do that, we can define.
And we can define the.
Let me just scroll down here.
We can go ahead and define the page meta.
This is something that is auto imported.
And over here, we're going to call it, and we're going to pass in the object, which is going to be
the meta.
And we're going to specify the layout.
And the layout is going to be the name of the file, in this case, custom.
So let's go ahead and actually save this.
And if I were to refresh.
You can see we get this really wonky effect.
And the reason why we're getting this effect here is now what we're going to need to do is remove this
right here.
So let's remove this div because we don't need that anymore.
And if I were to save it now you can see it looks exactly the same, except it doesn't have the knife
bar.
So it's very important to understand that what we did here was we overwritten the default layout, so
we're not going to be using that anymore.
So if we still want to have the nav bar in our custom layouts, we're going to need to specify it.
So very simply, we can just say here, nav bar like so.
And now we have our nav bar and over here you can see that the code is actually getting significantly
less.
It's a lot nicer now.
We don't have that big div that's in our way.
We just have the parent div and we have all of this content as well.
So you can see our code is getting significantly cleaner and we can do it.
Of course the exact same thing over here.
So we can instead say, define uh and then it was cost or defined page meta.
And over here we can say layout.
I'm going to say custom.
And now we can go ahead and just remove this div.
So let's remove that div.
We'll remove this.
And there we go.
That's pretty much all it is that we need to do.
So now, if I were to go to here and let's just say Houston, Houston and search and you can see that
it looks a little bit wonky here.
So let's see why that is so define page meta.
We have the layout.
Let's do a refresh.
There we go.
So so it was just wasn't refreshed.
So you can see here now it is indeed working and we have significantly reduced the complexity of our
code.