Another thing that I would like to clean up is this right over here?
So you can see that this function, we're using it in multiple different places.
So we're using it right over here in this page.
We're also using it right over here in this page.
So what I would like to do is kind of abstract it and put it in one file so we can just use it and import
it into the files that we need.
And what we can do is we can actually store this function, this functionality that we're going to utilize
throughout multiple different components or pages or both.
We can actually store them in composable so composable sort of places where we can store state as well
as a different pieces of functionality.
So I'm going to go over here, I'm going to create a composable directory and it has to be called composable
because Knox is going to understand that all of the different files in here are composable and do the
auto importing and I'm going to call this composable file use utility.
So typically composable start with use.
And over here I'm going to say use U DT Lee.
I'm a I'm trying to spell this correctly.
Utilities.
I think that's how you spell it.
And then when I say dot JS, so this is just going to be a regular function that we are going to export.
So we're going to say use utilities and this is just going to be a regular function like so and we're
going to grab this piece of functionality which is going to be the two title case and we're going to
place that in there.
And then at the very bottom of the function, we're going to return it.
So we're going to say to Title case.
So everything should be working A-OK now.
But now what we can do is instead of defining the function over here, what we can do is actually utilize
that composable so we can say const curly braces for do structuring, use utilities, and we can go
ahead and invoke it and we can actually get to title case that to title case function.
And now we can go ahead and remove this.
And now if I were to actually refresh, you can see that everything is still capitalized in the tab
and we can actually do the exact same thing.
Now, in the other case where we use it, which is going to be the this file right over here.
So over here we have use title case.
And we use that right over here in the use head as well.
So instead, I'm going to go ahead and just paste that in there and I'm going to remove this, save
that, and I'm going to go to G.
Let's go to slash car slash Jeep slash one, and you can see that Jeep is still capitalized.
So we can use comparables to kind of abstract away all of this repetitive code, which is always great.